There is now no doubt this president will go down in history as a peacemaking president.
Whether the Democrats like it or not, President Trump, again, will join us in a few moments
with details and more on this massive development and this breaking news.
It's good for the entire world.
Yes!
Thank you.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
All right, and on your way out, don't forget to help yourself to the bucket of crawdads.
Happy Wednesday, everyone.
So CNN's Caitlin Collins revealed staffers secretly dread traveling with President Trump
because he does not sleep.
Conversely, Biden's staffers dreaded traveling with Joe because he does not wipe.
It's day eight of the government shutdown.
It's getting scary.
They're already considering getting a backup generator for Mitch McConnell.
They say the shutdown could cost the economy approximately $15 billion a week.
To put that in perspective, that's $15 billion more than Kilmeade's book sales.
After receiving criticism for height-shaming, AOC now claims she actually loves short people.
In fact, she's hiding three of them in her ass.
It's a compliment.
KFC is once again offering its original honey barbecue flavor.
In a related story, guess who just bought four metric tons of napkins?
We'll see who just bought fourhoramoids you guys are choosing a canal of Australians.